surfstitch.com 2016-11-08

# SurfStitch | Online Shopping - Womens & Mens Surf Clothing & Fashion

Your privacy is of the utmost importance to us.

## SurfStitch Privacy Policy

This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for SurfStitch (including the SurfStitch Website at SurfStitch.com) - what information we gather, how we handle it and how to correct or change it.  

Other third party sites (including those partners, advertisers, sites or services to which the SurfStitch Website links or is otherwise connected) may have their own privacy policies and practices, which we do not control. 

### General Privacy Information

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information on any online service or website - for example on message boards, through email, or in chat areas - that information can be collected and used by others. 

In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. Further, while we take reasonable steps to protect your personal information once it is in our possession, SurfStitch cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us before it reaches us, and you do so at your own risk. You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information.

Please be careful and responsible whenever you are online. 

### Collection, Use and Disclosure of Information

Much of the information SurfStitch collects is "aggregated" -- meaning that the information from many users is grouped together in a way that does not reveal the personal information of any particular user. We may use this aggregated information to evaluate which products and services are successful and which ones are not, and in order to evaluate which new services we should make available on SurfStitch. We may also use the anonymous click stream data to help our advertisers deliver better-targeted advertisements.

In certain circumstances, SurfStitch may collect personal information about you, for example when you create an account, contact us, enter a competition, make a purchase or join a mailing list. The types of personal information we may collect includes your name, contact details, payment details and enquiry or complaint details. We also collect personal information through our records of your transactions and interactions (including by email, phone and online) with SurfStitch or on the SurfStitch Website. We collect personal information from you and in some cases from third parties including our related companies, your representatives and public sources.

We collect and use your personal information to provide, administer, improve and personalise the SurfStitch Website and our products and services, to run competitions, conduct surveys, process payments and refunds, understand you better, maintain and update our records, complete registrations, verify your identity, train and manage our people, protect our lawful interests and facilitate any acquisitions or potential acquisitions of our business. We may not be able to do these things without your personal information. For example, we may not be able to deliver your orders or respond to your enquiries.

We may exchange personal information with our related companies and with third party service providers who assist us with payment, marketing, data processing, IT, archival, auditing, accounting, customer contact, legal, business consulting, banking, delivery, data analysis, document management, research, investigation, insurance, website and other services. Some of these third parties may be located in Australia, USA, EU countries and other countries. 

### Cookies

**What are cookies?**

A cookie is a small data file that certain websites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a member ID that the site uses to track the pages you've visited. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites.

**Our cookies policy**

To make full use of the online shopping and personalised features on surfstitch.com, your computer, tablet or mobile phone will need to accept cookies, as we can only provide you with certain personalised features of the SurfStitch Website by using them.

Cookies work by assigning a unique number to the user that has no meaning outside the assigning site. This random number lets us keep track of "how many" times customers are doing specific things - like visiting our site each month - without knowing who those individual customers are. We use cookies to keep track of your shopping cart and to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. We also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, including via email, and to save your member ID.

Additionally, after you've entered your contact and delivery details during a session on our service, you can elect to save that information so you don't have to re-enter it when you return to the site. If you do not want this information to be saved, you must select "DO NOT SAVE DETAILS" when prompted. 

Our cookies do not store sensitive information such as your name, address or payment details. Rather, they just associate your member ID with this information once you’re logged in. However, if you'd prefer to restrict, block or delete cookies from the SurfStitch Website, you can use your browser to do so. Each browser is different, so check the 'Help' menu of your particular browser (or your mobile phone's handset manual) to learn how to change your cookie preferences.

**3rd party cookies**

The third party services we use include Google Analytics, Kamplye, DGM, Criteo and Commission Factory. These services may use cookies and other technologies such as web beacons and JavaScript on the SurfStitch website. This allows the collection of information about your use of our website (including your device’s IP address) in order to deliver customised advertising content, measure the effectiveness of advertising and provide other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Those third parties may also transfer the information they collect to others if required to do so by law, or where those others process the information on their behalf.

SurfStitch participates in some third party ‘online behavioural advertising’ (OBA), on a non-personally identifiable basis. This allows online advertising displayed to you to be tailored according to your browsing behaviour on various websites, not just our own. You can find you more details about OBA, the best practice guidelines and how to opt out from OBA with participating companies at the industry website www.youronlinechoices.com.au.

Additionally, SurfStitch cannot control the use of cookies or the resulting information by advertisers or third parties hosting data for SurfStitch. For example, if you take the opportunity to 'share’ SurfStitch content with friends through social networks such as Facebook or Twitter, you may be sent cookies from these websites. We suggest you check the third-party websites directly for more information about their cookies and how to manage them.

**Google Analytics Advertiser Features**

SurfStitch has the following Google Analytics Advertiser Features enabled:

\- Remarketing with Google Analytics

\- Google Display Network Impression Reporting

\- Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting

This enables Google Analytics to collect data about SurfStitch Website traffic via Google advertising cookies and anonymous identifiers, in addition to data collected through a standard Google Analytics implementation.

You can opt-out of the Google Analytics Advertiser Features you use, through your browser’s Ads Settings, Ad Settings for mobile apps, or by visiting the [_**Network Advertising Initiative**_](https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) website. To prevent your data being used by Google Analytics altogether, you can download and install the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on available here: [_**tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/**_](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/)

### Competitions

The majority of the contests that we offer are hosted on the SurfStitch server; however, there may be cases in which a third party sponsor will host the contest and collect user information. In those cases, we urge users to review the privacy statement of the third party site. Users may opt out of receiving future mailings.

### Newsletter and Marketing Communications

We offer a number of free newsletters to share content information about our site with interested users. There may be cases in which some of your personal information may be used by SurfStitch on an ongoing basis to target e-commerce promotions and telemarketing activities unless you opt out or we are prevented by law. For example, when you register as a user or check out as a guest on SurfStitch's main and/or partner websites, we may use your personal information to send you marketing and/or promotional materials from time to time. Users may elect to stop receiving marketing communications at any time by following the simple instructions at the bottom of the newsletter or communication or by contacting us as set out below.

### Online Security

SurfStitch utilizes a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. All user contact information is contained behind a "firewall" and only accessible by a limited number of employees who have special access rights to production systems. We generally store personal information in electronic form, but may also store some hard copy information. We store personal information at our own premises and with the assistance of our service providers. 

Credit card numbers are not stored in our systems in accordance with the highest of PCI-DSS standards. When purchasing from SurfStitch your financial details are passed through to a secure server using the latest 256-bit SSL (secure sockets layer) encryption technology.

If you choose to modify your personal information, you may do so by visiting the SurfStitch member page. You will be required to submit a valid member ID and password for authentication before you will be able to modify your file. Because password and credit card information has been encrypted, it is completely invisible, including to our customer service team.

SurfStitch's technology department conducts frequent site security audits and SurfStitch employs a third party audit company to perform additional site security audits.

### Additional Information for Investors

If you are investor in SurfStitch (or apply to be one), we may collect information about you through subscription agreements and other related documents and forms, including information about your transactions with us and our related bodies corporate. We collect, use and disclose that information to assess your application, manage your investment with us and provide investor services. We may exchange your personal information with our share registry providers and they may also exchange your personal information with other service providers. Please see the ‘Investors’ section of the SurfStitch Website for more information about our share registry provider and how to contact them. We are required or authorised to collect investor information under certain laws including the Income Tax Assessment Act and the Corporations Act, and we are also required to make limited shareholder details available to members of the public on request.

### Privacy Act

Nothing in this privacy policy is intended to limit our obligations or permitted handling of personal information under the Privacy Act and other applicable laws. We aim to ensure that our privacy policy continually meets all legal requirements in order to maintain and honour your privacy.

Please contact us as set out below if you have any questions about this privacy policy, the practices of SurfStitch with respect to personal information, or if you have any queries or concerns about your dealings with the SurfStitch Website or our handling of your information. If you express any concerns that we have interfered with your privacy we will promptly respond to let you know who will be handling your matter and when you can expect a response.  

You can also contact us as set out below if you wish to access or correct any personal information we hold about you. We may need to verify you identity. If we deny any request to access or correct personal information, we will provide our reasons. Where we decide not to make a requested correction to your personal information, you may ask us to note your request with the information. 

Contact: Privacy Officer.

Email: CustomerService@Surfstitch.com

Phone: 1800 172 208 (Australia only) or +617 5507 0499

For more information about the Privacy Act, or if your concern is not resolved to your satisfaction, you may contact the Privacy Commissioner on 1300 363 992 or [//www.privacy.gov.au ](https://www.privacy.gov.au/)

Surfstitch Pty Limited

ABN 48 602 288 004
